President Seibert, listen to reason.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yeah, I understand
I don't use the parking spot.
That's not the point. L...
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yes, I'm aware you told me
not to call you at home.
(Sheldon(on phone):)But you didn't answer the door.
(Sheldon(on phone):)And I know you were there
because I saw you through the mail slot.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yeah, well, that's some salty language.
May I remind you, you're the president
of a major university...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...not the president
of the Potty Mouth Club.
(Sheldon(on phone):)There it is again.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Do you kiss your mother
with that mouth?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Oh. Well, I'm sorry for your loss.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Good night, sir.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Unbelievable.
(Sheldon(on phone):)He says Wolowitz deserves my spot...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...because he's a high-profile asset
to the university.
(Leonard:)Well, he's not wrong. Howard did go
to the International Space Station.
(Sheldon:)That was five weeks ago.
(Sheldon:)How much longer
is he gonna milk that cow?
(Leonard:)Sheldon, let it go. It's not a big deal.